(Howard:)Hang on.
Are you saying the rest of us are dogs?
l can see you're gonna
take this the wrong way.
(Sheldon:)Let me try again.
lmagine
you're the sole human being...
(Sheldon:)...living on a planet
populated with nothing but chimps.
(Howard:)Get out of my lab.
(Sheldon:)Oh, now,
they're so much smarter than dogs.
(Sheldon:)Have you seen them
on those little bicycles?
Get out!
- How about dolphins?
- Out!
(Leonard:)So come on,
how was the first day with Hawking?
(Howard:)It was great. We talked about movies.
(Raj:)Oh.
- l showed him some card tricks.
- Oh.
(Howard:)He even let me read a couple pages
from his new book.
(Raj:)Oh...
(Howard:)Something got you down there,
bunky?
(Sheldon:)Howard, please, I'm begging you.
(Leonard:)Raj, you're our group historian.
Has Sheldon ever begged before?
(Raj:)Three times.
(Raj:)He begged the Fox network
not to cancel Firefly.
(Raj:)He begged the TNT network
to cancel Babylon 5.